[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":571579,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":608478,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":15066,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":623548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":9900,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":633452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":37672,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":671128,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":9660,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":680793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1623,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":682420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get yo ur resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6449,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":688873,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1052,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":689930,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3773,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":693706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1  = 2 beca use 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":7147,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":700858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3003,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":703864,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1001,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":704869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with t he first  number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":707855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":981,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":708840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3005,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":711849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":938,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":712791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3105,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":715898,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1143,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":717045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":723096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1375,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":724475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, yo u subtra ct 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3530,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":728009,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2000,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":730013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":145335,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":875353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":109966,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":985322,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["4","2"],"rt":10484,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":995811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3414,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":999228,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4016,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":1003248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1142,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":1004395,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What  is the  inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3597,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":1007995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1347,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":1009347,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2998,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":1012348,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1250,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":1013602,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4515,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":1018122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1410,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1019537,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":3405,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1022945,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub> 6</sub>.  <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":16600,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1039549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4747,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1044300,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1134,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1045438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1047632,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":896,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1048532,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1966,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1050505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":5326,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1055835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":1892,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1057731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1144,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1058879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After th at, try  to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":2217,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1061099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4552,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1065655,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1092,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1066751,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5210,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1071966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7  +<sub>9 </sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6381,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1078351,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1084022,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1086737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1090036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It's 5 because you add 4 and 1 and since it's less than 9 it stays 5","response_history":["5","It's 5 because you add 4 and 1 and since it's less than 9 it stays 5"],"rt":19489,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1109529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8 plus 4 is 12 and so you subtract 9 to get 3","response_history":["8 plus 4 is 12 and so you subje","8 plus 4 is 12 and so you subj","8 plus 4 is 12 and so you subtract 9 to get 3"],"rt":16453,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1125986,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"I think its 0 and I cna't remember how to explain it","response_history":["0","I think its 0 and I cna't remember how to explain it"],"rt":33461,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1159451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4 because you add 4 to 5 to get 9 which means you take away 9 to get 0","response_history":["4 because you add 4 to 5 to get 9 which means you take away 9 to get 0"],"rt":15162,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1174618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":" free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7 because that equals 9 and then you subtract 9 to get 0","response_history":["7 because that q","7 because that equals 9 and then you subtract 9 to get 0"],"rt":15538,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1190160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 is always 0 because I think that's what it said","response_history":["0 ","0","0","9 because that give syou ","0 ai","0 a","0 is always 0 because I think that's what it said"],"rt":25104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1215268,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 p lus 3 eq uals 9 and then you get 0","response_history":["6 plus 3 equals 9 and then you get 0"],"rt":11477,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1226749,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know this part confused me","response_history":["I don't know this part confused me"],"rt":15911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1242664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know this part confused me","response_history":["I don't know this part confused me"],"rt":2691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1245359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know this part confused me","response_history":["I don't know this part confused me"],"rt":2302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1247666,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know this part confused me","response_history":["I don't know this part confused me"],"rt":2258,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1249929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n  could be  any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":162421,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1412353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":12347,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1424705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I don't understand any of this","response_history":["I don't understand any of this"],"rt":12851,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1437561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't understand any of this","response_history":["I don't understand any of this"],"rt":4484,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1442048,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":2888,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1444940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator un der +<su b>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":2168,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1447113,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":2665,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1449782,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I don't understand any of this","response_history":["I d on't understand any of this"],"rt":2656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1452442,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6731,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1459177,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I don't understand any of this","response_history":["I don't understand any of this"],"rt":2356,"trial_type":"que stion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1461543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":8076,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1469624,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1276,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1470905,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"38","response_history":["38"],"rt":3895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1474804,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Associates Degree","response_history":["Associates Degree"],"rt":2675,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1477484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"college algebra and statistics","response_history":["collee","college algebra and statistics"],"rt":10318,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1487805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1490928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3489,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1494420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3446,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1497871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3108,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1500984,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4602,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1505590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2271,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1507866,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":6927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1514797,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":3563,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1518365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The first part was easier but then I was totally lost at the end, please don't hold that against me!","response_history":["The first part was easier but then I was totally lost at the end, please don't hold that against me!"],"rt":16993,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1535362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]